<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SportscultApp</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="history">Our History</string>
    <string name="content_history">Founded with a Mission to ‘Make Sports a Culture’ and a belief that it’s never too early or too late to learn a sport, we deliver well-structured comprehensive programs suited for all ages and skill levels – be it amateurs, professionals or recreational and leisure. Great Quality Facilities, Standardized Training (in skill and fitness), balanced nutrition guidance and technology driven assessment process are the cornerstones of Sports Cult’s training programs.</string>
    <string name="philosophy">Our Philosophy</string>
    <string name="content_philosophy">Playing sports at any level is enjoyable and doing it regularly improves your overall personality and makes you a healthier person. Some of us take up a sport with a goal to become a champion. It is our endeavor to create a structured, scientific journey for you to reach your goal.</string>
    <string name="commitment">Our Commitment</string>
    <string name="content_commitment">SportsCult is committed to excellence in all aspects of sports education that provides an inspiring environment for high performance. This commitment includes the training curriculum, well qualified trainers / coaches as well as the sporting facility.</string>
    <string name="sponsors">Our Sponsors</string>
    <string name="backdrop_subtitle">We are thankful to</string>
    <string-array name="age_groups">
        <item>Select Age Group</item>
        <item>9yrs - 10yrs</item>
        <item>10yrs - 11yrs</item>
        <item>11yrs - 12yrs</item>
        <item>12yrs - 13yrs</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="google_maps_api_key">AIzaSyC2yoXfDPcWtYb39XoqWtMW1ek1OGFSNRM</string>

    <!-- Toolbar titles -->

    <!-- Navigation Drawer -->
    <string name="title_activity_main2">SFL 2017</string>
    <string name="rule1">All players, including substitution players are mandated to play only under their age group.</string>
    <string name="rule2">Each match will be of 45 minutes with 20 minutes for each half and 5 minutes of break.</string>
    <string name="rule3">The event is of league format. Thus, each team will play with each of the other team and points table will be maintained.</string>
    <string name="rule4">Each team can register with maximum of 12 players.</string>
    <string name="rule5">Only 3 substitutions will be allowed in each match. Each age group plays 7-a-side.</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="request_call">Request Call</string>
    <string name="reg_closed">Online Registrations have been closed.\nFor Offline registrations\n Please Contact \nMr. Jalaj at 9205-846-046</string>
    <string name="rule6">It is mandatory to play under the jerseys provided by SportsCult.</string>
    <string name="rule7">A copy of Aadhar card will be required to be submitted by each player as a proof of age.</string>
    <string name="about2">SFL provides opportunities to hundreds of players to experience real time competitive matches every Saturday from 8th April 2017 to 20th May 2017 at a prime location in Gurugram in a brand new football field.</string>
    <string name="about3">Exposure to higher number of real-time matches.</string>
    <string name="about4">Best players will receive a free session with the Senior coaches at SportsCult.</string>
    <string name="about5">Motivating rewards to the top three teams.</string>
    <string name="loading">loading</string>
    <string name="match_live">Live Match updates</string>
    <string name="new_score">Score Updates</string>
    <string name="live_score">live_score</string>
    <string name="live_match">live_match</string>

</resources>
